<acis:errors xmlns:acis="http://acis.openlib.org"
             xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform"
             >
  <!-- cardiff -->
  <!-- from ACIS::Web -->
  <acis:error id='screen-presentation-invalid'>
    <xsl:text>There was an internal error while generating the page.  Please let administrator know. </xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='sesssion-failure'>
    <xsl:text>Your session can not be loaded.  It is probably expired already.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <!-- from ACIS::Web::Handler::Authenticate -->
  <acis:error id='login-authentication-failed'>
    <xsl:text>Check your password.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='login-unknown-user'>
    <xsl:text>There is no such account in our service. Please check the email address you typed. Is it the one you used to register here?<br/><br/> You have to register (see link below) before you can login.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='login-bad-password'>
    <xsl:text>Please check your password.  What you just entered is incorrect for this account.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='password-confirmation-mismatch'>
    <xsl:text>You typed different things in password and password confirmation. They must match.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='confirmation-bad'>
    <xsl:text>Sorry, this confirmation is wrong. Maybe you or somebody else have already confirmed your registration?</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='confirmation-account-clash'>
    <xsl:text>Sorry, your registration cannot be confirmed, because such account already exists.  Did you try to do two registrations in parallel (for the same email address)?  Tell the administrator why would you want to do it.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='confirmation-obstructed' >
    <xsl:text>Your registration cannot be finalized now.  You did everything correctly, but an internal technical problem happened.  The administrator will have to clear the issue.  We logged details of the problem and your email address.  <strong>The administrator will contact you as soon as the issue is resolved.</strong>  </xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='login-taken'>
    <xsl:text>The login you tried to change your account to is occupied already.  Please enter another email address.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='login-account-damaged'>
    <xsl:text>Your account record in the system is damaged.  Please notify the system administrator.  He should be able to restore it.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='login-account-locked'>
    <xsl:text>Your account is now locked by some other user (or may be yourself). Try again later.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='session-wrong-type'>
    <xsl:text>Either there is a serious system-misconfiguration or you are trying to see what you shouldn't. Please report to administrator if you didn't do anything special to see this. </xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='db-select-error'>
    <xsl:text>Internal database error.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='photo-cgi-error'>
    <xsl:text>Sorry, internal CGI error.  May be try again or ask the administrator for help.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='photo-cannot-open-file'>
    <xsl:text>Sorry, there is a system misconfiguration problem.  Please report to it to the  administrator.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='photo-image-unknown-format'>
    <xsl:text>Please upload GIF, JPEG, PNG or BMP picture.  The name of the file must have a corresponding extension.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='short-id-required'>
    <xsl:text>This operation cannot be done now, due to an internal problem.  You didn't do anything wrong.  Administrator should check your account and come back to you when its fixed.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <!-- <acis:error id='screen-not-found'>
       <xsl:text>Invalid page address.  There is no door on this side of the house.  Why knock?</acis:error>
  <xsl:text>-->
  <acis:error id='screen-not-found'>
    <xsl:text>Invalid page address.  Such screen doesn't exist. </xsl:text>
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <xsl:text>If you do not understand why you might be shown this error, </xsl:text>
    <big>
      <xsl:text>take note of the address of this page</xsl:text>
    </big>
    <xsl:text>and report it to administrator.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='bad-old-pass'>
    <xsl:text>Please give your actual current password. If you want to change it, there's no other way.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='session-failure'>
    <xsl:text>This session has already been closed.  If you had any changes in your account, they have been saved.  Please, login again.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='back-search-contributions-failed'>
    <xsl:text>We failed when tried to launch the automatic search for your research works.  It is not your fault.  You may contact the administrator for quicker resolution.  We are sorry.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='account-exists-already'>
    <xsl:text>Account with such name (email) already exists in the system.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='auto-search-start-failed'>
    <xsl:text>An attempt to start automatic search for your works failed.</xsl:text>
  </acis:error>
  <acis:error id='need-4-variations'>
    You need to have at least four name variations. By default, the
    system provides four. Amend those and add more, if necessary. We
    need all possible ways your name may appear in bibliographies and
    citations.
  </acis:error>
  
  <acis:error id='reset-token-expired'
  >Sorry, the reset link has already expired. You need to use the reset 
  link within 12 hours of requesting it.</acis:error>

  <acis:error id='reset-token-reused'
  >Sorry, the reset link has already been used. You need to request 
  another one.</acis:error>

  <acis:error id='reset-token-bad'
  >Sorry, the reset link is incorrect.</acis:error>

</acis:errors>
