<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<errors>

 <!-- from ACIS::Web -->

 <error id='screen-presentation-invalid'>There was an internal error
 while generating the page.  Please let administrator know.</error>

 <error id='sesssion-failure'>Your session can't be loaded.  It is probably
    expired already.</error>


 <!-- from ACIS::Web::Handler::Authenticate -->
 <error id='login-authentication-failed'>Check your password.</error>


 <error id='login-unknown-user'>There is no such account in our service.
 Please check the email address you typed.
 Is it the one you used to register here?<br/><br/>
 You have to register (see link below) before you can
 login.</error>


 <error id='login-bad-password'>Please check your password.  What you just
 entered is incorrect for this account.</error>


 <error id='password-confirmation-mismatch'>You typed different 
 things in password and password confirmation. They must match.</error>
 
 <error id='confirmation-bad'>Sorry, this confirmation is wrong.  Maybe you or
 somebody else have already confirmed your registration?</error>

 <error id='confirmation-account-clash'>Sorry, your registration cannot be
 confirmed, because such account already exists.  Did you try to do two
 registrations in parallel (for the same email address)?  Tell the
 administrator why would you want to do it.</error>


 <error id='confirmation-obstructed' >Your registration cannot be finalized
 now.  You did everything correctly, but an internal technical problem
 happened.  Administrator will have to clear the issue.  We logged details of
 the problem and your email address.  <strong>Administrator will contact you as
 soon as the issue is resolved.</strong>  
 </error>

 <error id='login-taken'>The login you tried to change your account to is
 occupied already.  You can't do that.</error>

 <error id='login-account-damaged'>Your account record in the system is
 damaged.  Please notify system administrator.  He should be able to restore
 it.</error>

 <error id='login-account-locked'>Your account is now locked by some other user
 (or may be yourself). Try again later.</error>

 

 <error id='session-wrong-type'>Either there is a serious
 system-misconfiguration or you are trying to see what you shouldn't.
 Please report to administrator if you didn't do anything special to see this.
 </error>


 <error id='db-select-error'>Internal database error.</error>

 <error id='photo-cgi-error'>Sorry, internal CGI error.  May be try again or
 ask admin for help.</error>

 <error id='photo-cannot-open-file'>Sorry, there is a system
 misconfiguration problem.  Please report to administrator.</error>

 <error id='photo-image-unknown-format'>Please upload GIF, JPEG, PNG or BMP
 picture.  The name of the file must have a corresponding extension.</error>

 <error id='short-id-required'>This operation cannot be done now, due
 to an internal problem.  You didn't do anything wrong.  Administrator
 should check your account and come back to you when its
 fixed.</error>

<!--
 <error id='screen-not-found'>Invalid page address.  There is no door on this
 side of the house.  Why knock?</error>
-->

<error id='screen-not-found'>Invalid page address.  Such screen doesn't exist.
<br/><br/> If you don't understand why you might be shown this error, <big>take
note of the address of this page</big> and report it to administrator.</error>


 <error id='bad-old-pass'>Please give your actual current password.
 If you want to change it, there's no other way.</error>

 <error id='session-failure'>This session has already been closed.  If you had
 any changes in your account, they have been saved.  Please, login
 again.</error>

 <error id='back-search-contributions-failed'>We failed when tried to launch
 the automatic search for your research works.  It is not your fault.  You may
 contact the administrator for quicker resolution.  We are sorry.</error>

 <error id='account-exists-already'>Account with such name (email) already
 exists in the system.</error>

 <error id='auto-search-start-failed'>An attempt to start automatic search for
 your works failed.</error>

</errors>